http://caje-miami.org/privacy/

CAJE Miami Privacy Policy
This Website is owned and operated by the Center for the Advancement of Jewish Education (the "CAJE Miami"). We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
Center for the Advancement of Jewish Education 4200 Biscayne Boulevard Miami, Florida 33137-3279 or e-mail us at: webmaster@caje-miami.org We'll be happy to answer your questions or address your concerns.
Our Policy
CAJE Miami uses its best efforts to respect the privacy of its online visitors. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is not to collect personal information about you when you visit our website unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.
When you visit our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our website. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.
CAJE Miami only gathers personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. For example, personally identifiable information may be collected in order to register online for classes or to make a donation online. If you choose to share personal information with us - by sending us a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information - we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized or in support of CAJE sponsored programs. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with Florida's archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to other third parties or government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law or in support of CAJE sponsored programs.
In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our website by collecting information on the date, time and website pages accessed by visitors to the website. We do this so we can improve the content of our website and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected and individual visitors' personal information is not identified.
Is Credit Card Information Secure?
We care about the safety and security of your transaction. [We use high grade encryption and the https security protocol to communicate with your browser software.] This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us. Contributions may also be made by calling 305-576-4030.
How Do We Use "Cookies"?
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected by the Federation's Website through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a Website can use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor's ongoing access to and use of the site, and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature. CAJE Miami uses "cookie" technology only to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors in order to improve visitors' online experience and facilitate their visit within our site.
Note to Parents on Our Privacy Policy
CAJE Miami welcomes children to learn more about our organization and, where appropriate, find opportunities to serve their communities through CAJE programs and activities. However, we encourage this to be done only with their parent's knowledge and supervision. [For this reason, CAJE Miami follows the guidelines for interactive electronic media published by the Children's Advertising Review Unit of the Better Business Bureau.]
Special notices urging children to get their parent's permission before providing any personal information have been incorporated into our site.
For information about CAJE Miami and its mission, or to learn about legal or technical issues regarding the use of this site, you can read the fine print.
And if you would like to contact us at any time during your visit, just click Contact Us at the bottom of every page.
Upcoming Events
Latest News
Behave Like Israel
I find Parashat Vayishlach very applicable to some of the unresolved issues that we are going through today. We find Jacob going back home after 20 years. And for us, the year 2020 feels like 20 years in one!
More News »
Gifts We Will Take with Us… After the Pandemic
Covid-19 has changed the way we do many things. Yet one factor remains the same: our early childhood educators’ commitment to the children and their families and to creating and nurturing relationships that become the beginning of many family’s Jewish journey.
More News »
Is Thanksgiving Jewish?
Is Thanksgiving Jewish? Of course! Want to know how? Read on. On Thursday, we will pause and take a moment to say thanks. One of the perennial questions asked: Is Thanksgiving Jewish? We have a great answer, courtesy of Moshe Sokolow, professor of Jewish education at the Azrieli Graduate School of Yeshiva University...
More News »
More News »
© 2020 Center for Advancement of Jewish Education (CAJE). All rights reserved. CAJE is a subsidiary agency of the Greater Miami Jewish Federation.
Powered by ARCOS | Design by Plus Three
